It's actually quite straightforward to make your apps content provider
当你打算让你应用的content provider(内容提供)可以在第三方的应用时，上述方法
available to third party apps. The key is to modify
是很直接的。 关键是需要修改
the export flag in the manifest entry here to true.
在manifest文件中的export flag（输出指标）成 ture(正值)
As simple as that. Any app that knows the content URI
就这么简单。任何一个应用会知道内容URI
can use the content resolve or access it the same
可以使用哪些内容来解决或者访问它。这跟你做的时
that you do. Now depending on the sensitivity of your
一样的。 现在关于你这些数据的敏感程度
data, you may want to protect it by requiring specific
你想要对这些数据在访问或者修改时
permissions to read or write to the database. So if you
进行分级管理。所以如果你想这么做
want to, you can effectively limit access only to other
你可以对你自己创建的或者第三方的应用设置
apps you have created, or to third party apps, which know
访问限制，这样就可以来掌握
the permissions and users agree to. Then you just need to
访问权限了。下一步你需要做的是
publish this contract, to interact with the content provider, specifically the
公开这些访问权限的合约， 通过和内容提供者的互动，尤其是
URI and column names. And you've created a simple API
URI 和 数据列的名称。这样你已经为你的数据创建了一个
for all of your data. And as simple as that, you've
简单的API。就这么容易，你已经为你自己的数据创建了这个
created a new API, just for your data. This is exactly
新的API。这个方法其实和很多ative content providers（本地内容提供者）
the same approach, used by many of the native content providers,
所使用的方法是一样的。
including the Contacts Database, Media Store, Calendar and Call Log.
包括了Contacts Database(合约数据库)，Media Store(媒体库),日历和调用日志.